you're used to asking questions to
uncover the insights you need and
solving problems by chatting with
co-workers customers or vendors now
co-pilot in Microsoft Dynamics 365
business Central offers you a new way to
continue the
conversation co-pilot is your everyday
AI companion for work built on
Microsoft's industry leading privacy and
security it's here to help you find the
answers to your questions quickly and
easily For the First Time Business
Central users are empowered to interact
with their data using their own words
use co-pilot to skip traditional menu
navigation and locate records faster
didn't find exactly what you were
looking for you can ask follow-up
questions to clarify and refine your
[Music]
search co-pilot X as a virtual assistant
helping you track down the right
information at the right time all using
natural language
even complex searches become easy get
answers to questions on how when or why
to do
things so new users can get up to speed
quickly and longtime employees can learn
new skills co-pilot gives your employees
an edge by Leading them to the next step
so processes are easier to learn and
problems are easier to solve with
everyday bringing something new co-pilot
helps you reclaim time so you can work
work smarter adapt faster and perform
better be ready for what's next with
Dynamix 365 business
Central